Guide to the Time Inc. Annex Files 1854, 1909, 1923-2014 MS 3009-RG 39
New-York Historical Society
- Time-Life Films: Titles: Walking Through Fire, 1979 (Offsite-box 4005, Folder 11)
- Time-Life Films: Titles: Wall, The, 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 4005, Folder 12)
- Time-Life Films: Titles: Wall, The [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Offsite-box R84)
- Time-Life Films: Titles: Wild World of Animals, 1978 (Offsite-box 4005, Folder 13)
- Time-Life Films: Titles: Winds of War, The (Not Done by Time-Life Films), 1976-1978 (Offsite-box 4005, Folder 14)
- Time-Life Films: Titles: World War II: GI Diary, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 4005, Folder 15)
- Time-Life Films: Titles: You Have Seen Their Faces, 1978 (Offsite-box 4005, Folder 16)
- Time-Life News Service: Domestic Cities: Chicago, 1946-1948, 1961 (Offsite-box 4005, Folder 17)
- Time-Life News Service: Domestic Cities: Detroit, 1954 (Offsite-box 4005, Folder 18)
- Time-Life News Service: Domestic Cities: Los Angeles, 1943, 1946, 1949, 1951, 1954, 1960 (Offsite-box 4005, Folder 19)
- Time-Life News Service: Domestic Cities: Miami, 1959 (Offsite-box 4005, Folder 20)
- Time-Life News Service: Domestic Cities: San Francisco, 1942-1946, 1959 (Offsite-box 4005, Folder 21)
- Time-Life News Service: Domestic Cities: Seattle, 1959 (Offsite-box 4005, Folder 22)
- Time-Life News Service: Domestic Cities: Washington, DC: Sample Dispatches, 1942, 1945 (Offsite-box 4005, Folder 23)
- Time-Life News Service: Domestic Cities: Washington, DC: Miscellaneous, 1942-46, 1950-51, 1960 (Offsite-box 4005, Folder 24)
- Time-Life News Service: Domestic: Desegregation Survey 1963 (Offsite-box 4005, Folder 25)
- Time-Life News Service: Domestic: Manuals, 1951-55, 1959 (Offsite-box 4005, Folder 26)
- Time-Life News Service: Domestic: Miscellaneous, 1940-1960 (Offsite-box 4005, Folder 27)
- Time-Life News Service: Foreign: Manuals, 1952, undated (Offsite-box 4005, Folder 28)
- Time-Life News Service: General Dispatches 1958 (Selected by Gottfried), 1959 (Offsite-box 4005, Folder 29-30)
- Time-Life: Retail: Magazine Rack Design, undated (Offsite-box 4045, Folder 10)
- Time-Life: Retail: Sales, 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 4045, Folder 11)
- Time Out, 1940-1950, 1968 (Offsite-box 4041, Folder 6)
- Time Understanding the 1961 Campaign, 1959, 1961 (Offsite-box 4005, Folder 31)
- Time Warner, 1991 (Offsite-box 4005, Folder 32)
- Time Warner: General, undated (Offsite-box 4041, Folder 7)
- Time Warner, Inc. Calendars, 1991 (Offsite-box 4005, Folder 33)
- Time Warner, Inc. Calendars 1993 (Offsite-box 4006, Folder 1-2)
- Time Warner, Inc. Calendars 1994 (Offsite-box 4006, Folder 3)
- Time Warner, Inc. Calendars (Samples) 1996- (Offsite-box 4006, Folder 4)
- Time Warner Top 100 Advertisers 2011 (Offsite-box 4041, Folder 8)
- Treasurer's Office: Five-Year Plan 1977-82 (Offsite-box 4006, Folder 5)
- Treasurer's Office: Statement of Income 1979, 1978 (Offsite-box 4006, Folder 6)
- Tribute to Luce, 1967 (Offsite-box 4008, Folder 6)
  2 audiotape reels: analog, 5 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label on container: "Tributes to H. Luce featuring A. Heiskell and J. Linen – WINS- Feb. 28/67"
  1 audiotape reel: analog, 5 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label on container: "Luce Tribute – WINS – 2/28/67"
- Truman, Harry S. Presidential Library Papers, 1943-1949, 1971 (Offsite-box 4041, Folder 10)
- TV-Cable Week Surveys and Studies TV Guide Competitive Analysis 1983 (Offsite-box 4006, Folder 7)
- University Studies and Theses University of Minnesota, 1955 (Offsite-box 4006, Folder 8-9)
- Warner Bros. Studio Stores Catalogs 1992-, 1992, 1994 (Offsite-box 4006, Folder 10)
- Washington Star Survey and Studies, 1966, 1970, 1979, 1970 (Offsite-box 4006, Folder 11-12)
- WINS Radio – "All About Life ", 1963 (Offsite-box 4008, Folder 7)
  1 audiotape reel: analog, 5 in., 1/4 in. tape. Label on container: "WINS radio feature about Life's "All About Life" Presentation 6/19/63"
- Yankelovich Historical Tracking Foreign Policy, 1990 (Offsite-box 4006, Folder 13-14)